A Guide to the Records of the Clan MacLeod Society USA, 1899-2009
Special Collections, Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Clan MacLeod USA 1952-2009.
  - Membership
    - Membership correspondence 1992 (Box-folder 16:20)
    - Membership correspondence 1993 (I) (Box-folder 16:21)
    - Membership correspondence 1993 (II) (Box-folder 16:22)
    - Membership correspondence 1993 (III) (Box-folder 17:1)
    - Membership correspondence 1994 (I) (Box-folder 17:2)
    - Membership correspondence 1994 (II) (Box-folder 17:3)
    - Membership correspondence 1994 (III) (Box-folder 17:4)
    - Membership correspondence 1994 (IV) (Box-folder 17:5)
    - Membership correspondence 1995 (I) (Box-folder 17:6)
    - Membership correspondence 1995 (II) (Box-folder 17:7)
    - Membership correspondence 1995 (III) (Box-folder 18:1)
    - Membership correspondence 1995 (IV) (Box-folder 18:2)
    - Membership correspondence 1996 (I) (Box-folder 18:3)
    - Membership correspondence 1996 (II) (Box-folder 18:4)
    - Membership correspondence 1996 (III) (Box-folder 18:5)
    - Membership correspondence 1997 (Box-folder 18:6)
    - Membership correspondence 1998 (I) (Box-folder 18:7)
    - Membership correspondence 1998 (II) (Box-folder 18:8)
    - Undated membership correspondence (Box-folder 18:9)
    - Blank membership forms (Box-folder 19:1)
    - Flowers of the Forest (deceased members) (Box-folder 19:2)
    - Highland Games packet: circuit packet of information for new members 1983 (Box-folder 19:3)
    - Letters to new members (Box-folder 19:4)
    - Membership directories 1978, 1979 (Box-folder 19:5)
    - Membership lists 1953-1954 (Box-folder 19:6)
    - Membership lists 1955-1962 (Box-folder 19:7)
    - Membership lists 1970s (Box-folder 19:8)
    - Membership lists 1980s (I) (Box-folder 19:9)
    - Membership lists 1980s (II) (Box-folder 19:10)
    - Membership lists 1980s (III) (Box-folder 19:11)
    - Membership lists 1990s (I) (Box-folder 20:1)
    - Membership lists 1990s (II) (Box-folder 20:2)
    - Membership lists 2000s (Box-folder 20:3)
    - Lists of deleted members (Box-folder 20:4)
    - Membership questions (copy) (Box-folder 20:5)
    - Membership status committee (Box-folder 20:6)
    - USA members on the roll in Edinburgh August 1963 (Box-folder 20:7)
    - Clan MacLeod register (blank) (Box-folder 20:8)
    - Clan MacLeod register (filled) (Box-folder 20:9)
    - Roster of visitors to Dunvegan Castle (Box-folder 20:10)
    - Septs of MacLeod/membership requirements (Box-folder 20:11)
  - Minutes and Agendas
    - Board Minutes 1954-1958 (Box-folder 20:12)
    - Clan Society Minutes 1959-1969 (Box Box 21 (Binder Case))
    - Agenda draft 1973 ? (Box-folder 22:1)
    - Agenda for planning session 1984 (Box-folder 22:2)
    - Discussion items for Clan MacLeod USA Meetings (Box-folder 22:3)
  - Newsletter
    - Newsletter correspondence 1957-1969 (Box-folder 22:4)
    - Newsletter correspondence 1980-1993 (Box-folder 22:5)
    - Newsletter correspondence 1994-2002 (Box-folder 22:6)
    - MacLeod newsletter extracts (Box-folder 22:7)
    - Newsletter reports (Box-folder 22:8)
    - Request for advertisers for Clan MacLeod Newsletter (Box-folder 22:9)
    - Winter Bulletin: Comings and Goings of the MacLeods 1956 (Box-folder 22:10)
    - Newsletter November 1957 (Box-folder 22:11)
    - Newsletter May 1958 (Box-folder 22:12)
    - Newsletter November 1958 (Box-folder 22:13)
    - Newsletter April 1959 (Box-folder 22:14)
    - Newsletter November 1959 (Box-folder 22:15)
    - Newsletter May 1960 (Box-folder 22:16)
    - Newsletter November 1960 (Box-folder 22:17)
    - Newsletter May 1961 (Box-folder 22:18)
    - Newsletter October 1961 (Box-folder 22:19)
    - Newsletter May 1962 (Box-folder 22:20)
    - Newsletter October 1962 (Box-folder 22:21)
    - Newsletter May 1963 (Box-folder 22:22)
    - Newsletter October 1963 (Box-folder 22:23)
    - Newsletter Spring 1964 (Box-folder 22:24)
    - Newsletter Fall 1964 (Box-folder 22:25)
    - Newsletter Spring 1965 (Box-folder 22:26)
    - Newsletter Fall 1965 (Box-folder 22:27)
    - Newsletter Spring 1966 (Box-folder 22:28)
    - Newsletter Fall 1966 (Box-folder 22:29)
    - Newsletter Spring 1967 (Box-folder 22:30)
    - Newsletter Fall 1967 (Box-folder 22:31)
    - Newsletter Spring 1968 (Box-folder 22:32)
    - Newsletter Fall 1968 (Box-folder 23:1)
    - Newsletter Spring 1969 (Box-folder 23:2)
    - Newsletter Fall 1969 (Box-folder 23:3)
    - Newsletter Spring 1970 (Box-folder 23:4)
    - Newsletter Fall 1970 (Box-folder 23:5)
    - Newsletter Spring 1971 (Box-folder 23:6)
    - Newsletter Fall 1971 (Box-folder 23:7)
    - Newsletter Summer 1972 (Box-folder 23:8)
    - Newsletter Fall 1972 (Box-folder 23:9)
    - Newsletter Spring 1973 (Box-folder 23:10)
    - Newsletter Fall 1973 (Box-folder 23:11)
    - Newsletter Spring 1974 (Box-folder 23:12)
    - Newsletter Winter 1974 (Box-folder 23:13)
    - Newsletter Summer 1975 (Box-folder 23:14)
    - Newsletter Summer 1976 (Box-folder 23:15)
    - Newsletter Winter 1976-1977 (Box-folder 23:16)
    - Newsletter Fall 1977 (Box-folder 23:17)
    - Newsletter Spring 1978 (Box-folder 23:18)
    - Newsletter Fall 1978 (Box-folder 23:19)
    - Newsletter Spring 1979 (Box-folder 23:20)
    - Newsletter Fall 1979 (Box-folder 23:21)
    - Newsletter Spring 1980 (Box-folder 23:22)
    - Newsletter Fall 1980 (Box-folder 23:23)
    - Newsletter Spring 1981 (Box-folder 23:24)
    - Newsletter Fall 1981 (Box-folder 23:25)
    - Newsletter Fall 1982 (Box-folder 23:26)
    - Newsletter Spring 1983 (Box-folder 24:1)
    - Newsletter Fall 1983 (Box-folder 24:2)
    - Newsletter Spring 1984 (Box-folder 24:3)
    - Newsletter Fall 1984 (Box-folder 24:4)
    - Newsletter Spring 1985 (Box-folder 24:5)
    - Newsletter Fall 1985 (Box-folder 24:6)
    - Newsletter Spring 1986 (Box-folder 24:7)
    - Newsletter Fall 1986 (Box-folder 24:8)
    - Newsletter Spring 1987 (Box-folder 24:9)
    - Newsletter Fall 1987 (Box-folder 24:10)
    - Newsletter Spring 1988 (Box-folder 24:11)
    - Newsletter Fall 1988 (Box-folder 24:12)
    - Newsletter Spring 1989 (Box-folder 24:13)
    - Newsletter Fall 1989 (Box-folder 24:14)
    - Newsletter Spring 1990 (Box-folder 24:15)
    - Newsletter Fall 1990 (Box-folder 24:16)
    - Newsletter Spring 1991 (Box-folder 24:17)
    - Newsletter Fall 1991 (Box-folder 24:18)
    - Newsletter Spring 1992 (Box-folder 24:19)
    - Newsletter Fall 1992 (Box-folder 24:20)
    - Newsletter Spring 1993 (Box-folder 24:21)
    - Newsletter Fall 1993 (Box-folder 24:22)
    - Newsletter Spring 1994 (Box-folder 24:23)
    - Newsletter Autumn 1994 (Box-folder 25:1)
    - Newsletter Spring 1995 (Box-folder 25:2)
    - Newsletter Autumn 1995 (Box-folder 25:3)
    - Newsletter Spring 1996 (Box-folder 25:4)
    - Newsletter Autumn 1996 (Box-folder 25:5)
    - Newsletter Spring 1997 (Box-folder 25:6)
    - Newsletter Autumn 1997 (Box-folder 25:7)
    - Newsletter Spring 1998 (Box-folder 25:8)
    - Newsletter Fall 1998 (Box-folder 25:9)
    - Newsletter Spring 1999 (Box-folder 25:10)
    - Newsletter Autumn 1999 (Box-folder 25:11)
    - Newsletter Spring 2000 (Box-folder 25:12)
    - Newsletter Autumn 2000 (Box-folder 25:13)
    - Newsletter Spring 2001 (Box-folder 25:14)
    - Newsletter Autumn 2001 (Box-folder 25:15)
    - Newsletter Spring/Summer 2002 (Box-folder 25:16)
    - Newsletter Pre-Parliament 2002 (Box-folder 25:17)
    - Newsletter Autumn/Winter 2002 (Box-folder 25:18)
    - Newsletter Spring 2003 (Box-folder 25:19)
    - Newsletter Spring 2004 (Box-folder 25:20)
    - Newsletter Autumn/Winter 2004 (Box-folder 25:21)
    - Newsletter: 50th USA Anniversary Dinner Winter/Spring 2005 (Box-folder 25:22)
    - Newsletter Autumn/Spring 2005, Spring 2005 Addendum (Box-folder 25:23)
    - Newsletter Summer/Fall 2005 (Box-folder 25:24)
    - Newsletter Winter/Spring 2006 (Box-folder 25:25)
    - Newsletter Winter/Spring 2006 (Box-folder 26:1)
    - Newsletter Spring/Winter 2007 (Box-folder 26:2)
    - Newsletter Fall/Winter 2007 (Box-folder 26:3)
    - Newsletter Spring 2008 (Box-folder 26:4)
    - Newsletter Spring 2008 (Box-folder 26:5)
  - North American Gathering
    - North American Gathering: Cornwall Ontario, Canada July 30-August 1, 1976 (Box-folder 27:1)
    - North American Gathering: Dearborn, Michigan 1980 (Box-folder 27:2)
    - North American Gathering: Nova Scotia 1984 (Box-folder 27:3)
    - North American Gathering: Chicago 1988 (Box-folder 27:4)
    - North American Gathering: Vancouver, British Columbia 1992 (Box-folder 27:5)
    - North American Gathering: Hudson Highland Dream, West Point, New York July 24-28, 1996 (Box-folder 27:6)
    - North American Gathering: Ontario, Canada 2000 (Box-folder 27:7)
    - North American Gathering: Chicago 2004 (Box-folder 27:8)
  - Old Dominion University and Archives
    - Correspondence regarding Old Dominion University archives 1980s (Box-folder 27:9)
    - Correspondence regarding Old Dominion University archives 1990s (Box-folder 27:10)
    - Dame Flora MacLeod of MacLeod Memorial Collection bookplate (Box-folder 27:11)
    - Dame Flora MacLeod Collection holdings at O.D.U. 1988 (Box-folder 27:12)
    - Institute of Scottish Studies at Old Dominion University Library (Box-folder 27:13)
    - Odum Genealogical Library: correspondence and information (Box-folder 27:14)
    - Sandhills Community College: correspondence and information (Box-folder 27:15)
    - Report of the historian regarding repository of historical records March 24, 1979 (Box-folder 27:16)
    - Executive summary of historian's report to council April 19, 1990 (Box-folder 27:17)
    - Historian's report for annual business meeting April 20, 1990 (Box-folder 27:18)
    - Historian's report to council, annual general meeting (bound copy) 1990 (Box-folder 27:19)
    - Historian's report to council (handwritten draft) 1990 (Box-folder 27:20)
    - Historian's mid-year report to council November 27, 1990 (Box-folder 27:21)
    - Historian's report 1991 (Box-folder 27:22)
    - Historian's report to council, annual general meeting(bound copy) 1993 (Box-folder 27:23)
    - Supplement to historian's report to council June 7, 1993 (Box-folder 27:24)
    - Historian's report to council Winter 1996 (Box-folder 27:25)
    - Historian's report to council June 15, 1997 (Box-folder 27:26)
    - Information: William Jefferson Bryson, Jr. (society archivist) (Box-folder 27:27)
    - List of books donated by Frances Pearson (Box-folder 27:28)
    - Taos Public Library (Box-folder 27:29)
  - Presidents
    - Presidential Files: J. Norman MacLeod (I) (Box Box 28 (Binder Case))
    - Presidential Files: J. Norman MacLeod (II) (Box Box 29 (Binder Case))
    - President?s monthly letters to clan members 1954-2003 (Box-folder 30:1)
    - President?s banquet address (undated) (Box-folder 30:2)
    - President and others abroad for news (Box-folder 30:3)
    - President?s annual report: John H. MacLeod January 27, 1956 (Box-folder 30:4)
    - Vice-President Activities 1968 (Box-folder 30:5)
    - Ray McCabe (Box-folder 30:6)
    - Past Presidents 1964-1967 (Box-folder 30:7)
  - Projects-Migration Project in regard to Clan MacLeod USA
    - Announcements (Box-folder 30:8)
    - Correspondence regarding the migration project (Box-folder 30:9)
    - Job description: migration project chairman (Box-folder 30:10)
    - Questionnaires (Box-folder 30:11)
    - Reports (Box-folder 30:12)
    - Genealogical requests (I) (Box-folder 30:13)
    - Genealogical requests (II) (Box-folder 30:14)
    - The Research Process (Box-folder 30:15)
    - Miscellaneous genealogical (Box-folder 30:16)
    - Bound book: Migration Project (Part I) 1972-1977 (Box Box 31)
    - Bound book: Migration Project (Part II) 1972-1977 (Box Box 31)
  - Projects-Miscellaneous
    - Appalachian State University marketing project 1990 (Box-folder 32:1)
    - Clan sept map project (Box-folder 32:2)
    - Council mail referenda (Box-folder 32:3)
    - Focus One questionnaire 1993 (Box-folder 32:4)
    - Future planning workshop, Appalachian State University Center for Continuing Education July 13, 1979 (Box-folder 32:5)
    - Microfilming projects (I) (Box-folder 32:6)
    - Microfilming projects (II) (Box-folder 32:7)
    - Publicity with the Old English Sheep dog Club (Box-folder 32:8)
  - Regional Societies
    - List of regional officers (Box-folder 32:9)
    - Regional organization (Box-folder 32:10)
    - Regional vice presidents (Box-folder 32:11)
    - Clan historian: Carolinas (Box-folder 32:12)
    - Correspondence: Carolinas (Box-folder 32:13)
    - Letterheads: Carolinas (Box-folder 32:14)
    - Membership in regard to Carolinas (Box-folder 32:15)
    - Newsletters: Carolinas (Box-folder 32:16)
    - Reports: Carolinas (Box-folder 32:17)
    - Correspondence: Great Lakes (Box-folder 32:18)
    - North-Central Region Letters Great Lakes (Box-folder 32:19)
    - Correspondence: Gulf Central (Box-folder 32:20)
    - Reports: Gulf Central (Box-folder 32:21)
    - Applicants: Mid-Atlantic vacancies (Box-folder 32:22)
    - Correspondence: Mid-Atlantic (Box-folder 32:23)
    - Events: Mid-Atlantic (Box-folder 32:24)
    - Newsletter: Mid-Atlantic (Box-folder 32:25)
    - Reports: Mid-Atlantic (Box-folder 32:26)
    - Correspondence: New England (Box-folder 32:27)
    - Reports: North Central (Box-folder 32:28)
    - Reports: North Central region structure (Box-folder 32:29)
    - Northeast Clan Coordinators (Box-folder 33:1)
    - Correspondence: Northeast (Box-folder 33:2)
    - Directories: Northeast (Box-folder 33:3)
    - Events: Northeast (Box-folder 33:4)
    - News Page: New York City and Central Regions (Northeast) October 16, 1964 (Box-folder 33:5)
    - Reports: Northeast (Box-folder 33:6)
    - Natterbox (Northeast newsletter) 1979-1980 (Box-folder 33:7)
    - Northeast newsletter 1989-1993 (Box-folder 33:8)
    - Northeast newsletter 1993-1997 (Box-folder 33:9)
    - News-update (Northeast newsletter) 1998-1999 (Box-folder 33:10)
    - Correspondence: Northwest (Box-folder 33:11)
    - News of the Western Region (Northwest newsletter) 1979-1982 (Box-folder 33:12)
    - Reports: Northwest (Box-folder 33:13)
    - Correspondence: Pacific (I) (Box-folder 33:14)
    - Correspondence: Pacific (II) (Box-folder 33:15)
    - Correspondence: Pacific (III) (Box-folder 33:16)
    - Newsletters: Pacific (Box-folder 33:17)
    - Pamphlets: Pacific (Box-folder 34:1)
    - Reports: Pacific (Box-folder 34:2)
    - Correspondence: South Central (Box-folder 34:3)
    - Newsletters: South Central (Box-folder 34:4)
    - Reports: South Central (Box-folder 34:5)
    - Correspondence: Southeast (Box-folder 34:6)
    - Southeastern Report (newsletter) (Box-folder 34:7)
    - Reports: Southeast (Box-folder 34:8)
    - Correspondence: Southwest (Box-folder 34:9)
    - Reports: Southwest (Box-folder 34:10)
  - Reports
    - Miscellaneous reports (Box-folder 34:11)
    - Bookkeeping journal kept by Laura Margaret MacLeod 1955-1960 (Box-folder 34:12)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society corresponding records 1976-1977,1978 (Box Box 34)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society records 1967-1972 (Box Box 34)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society records 1973-1974 (Box Box 35)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society records 1975-1977 (Box Box 35)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society records (Part 2) 1977 (Box Box 36)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society records (Part 1) 1978 (Box Box 37)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society records (Part 2) 1978 (Box Box 38)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society records (Part 1) 1979 (Box Box 39)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society records (Part 2) 1979 (Box Box 40)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society records, future planning projects 1979 (Box Box 40)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society records (Vol. I) 1980 (Box Box 41)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society records (Vol. II) 1980 (Box Box 41)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society miscellaneous records (Box Box 42)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society miscellaneous corresponding secretary records (part 1) 1980 (Box Box 43)
    - Bound book: Clan MacLeod Society miscellaneous corresponding secretary records (part 2) 1980 (Box Box 44)
  - Reports-Annual
    - Newsletter: Annual Report 1955 (Box-folder 45:1)
  - Reports-Membership Secretary
    - Reports 1978-1988 (Box-folder 45:2)
    - Reports 1989-1992 (Box-folder 45:3)
    - Reports 1993 (Box-folder 45:4)
    - Reports 1993-1994 (Box-folder 45:5)
    - Reports 1994-1995 (Box-folder 45:6)
    - Reports 1996-1997 (Box-folder 45:7)
    - Reports 1998-2000, 2003 (Box-folder 45:8)
  - Reports-Secretary
    - Secretary reports 1950s (Box-folder 46:1)
  - Reports-Treasurer
    - Reports 1955, 1959 (Box-folder 46:2)
    - Reports 1961, 1966 (Box-folder 46:3)
    - Reports 1977-1981 (Box-folder 46:4)
    - Reports 1982-1985 (Box-folder 46:5)
    - Reports 1986-1990 (Box-folder 46:6)
    - Reports 1991-1993 (Box-folder 46:7)
    - Reports 1994-1996 (Box-folder 46:8)
    - Reports 1999 (Box-folder 46:9)
    - Reports 2003-2004 (Box-folder 46:10)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Miscellaneous Clan Needs (Box-folder 47:1)
    - Clan MacLeod USA membership Cards (Box-folder 47:2)
    - Clan-Publicist Report December 1, 1990 (Box-folder 47:3)
- Personal Correspondence.
  This series contains the personal (non-administrative) correspondence of those within Clan MacLeod. The correspondence in this series consists of personal letters and cards (birthday, Christmas, and miscellaneous occasions). There are no sub-series within this series and correspondence is filed by alphabetical order.
  - Bryson, William Jefferson, Jr. (Box-folder 47:4)
  - Fraser,Ena (Box-folder 47:5)
  - Gordon, Joan Wolridge (Box-folder 47:6)
  - Link, Emma (Box-folder 47:7)
  - MacDonald-Millar, Reverend Donald (Box-folder 47:8)
  - MacLeod, Allan (Box-folder 47:9)
  - MacLeod, Andrew (Box-folder 47:10)
  - MacLeod, Anthony (Box-folder 47:11)
  - MacLeod, Dame Flora of MacLeod (Box-folder 47:12)
  - MacLeod, E.H. (Box-folder 47:13)
  - MacLeod, Harry G. (Box-folder 47:14)
  - MacLeod, John of MacLeod (Box-folder 47:15)
  - MacLeod, Isobel (Box-folder 47:16)
  - MacLeod, J. Norman (Box-folder 47:17)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (I) (Box-folder 47:18)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (II) (Box-folder 48:1)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (III) (Box-folder 48:2)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (IV) (Box-folder 48:3)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (V) (Box-folder 48:4)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (VI) (Box-folder 48:5)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (VII) (Box-folder 48:6)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (VIII) (Box-folder 49:1)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (IX) (Box-folder 49:2)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (X) (undated correspondence) (Box-folder 49:3)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (XI) (birthday cards) (Box-folder 49:4)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (XII) (Christmas cards) (Box-folder 49:5)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (XIII) (Christmas cards continued) (Box-folder 49:6)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (XIV) (Christmas cards continued) (Box-folder 49:7)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (XV) (Christmas cards continued) (Box-folder 49:8)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (XVI) (Christmas cards continued) (Box-folder 50:1)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (XVII) (Christmas cards continued) (Box-folder 50:2)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (XVIII) (Christmas cards continued) (Box-folder 50:3)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (XIX) (Christmas cards continued) (Box-folder 50:4)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (XX) (Easter cards) (Box-folder 50:5)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (XXI) (Halloween & Thanksgiving cards) (Box-folder 50:6)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (XXII) (Valentines cards) (Box-folder 50:7)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (XXIII) (miscellaneous cards) (Box-folder 50:8)
  - MacLeod, Laura Margaret (XXIV) (miscellaneous notes and scrap) (Box-folder 50:9)
  - MacLeod, Marietta (Box-folder 51:1)
  - MacLeod, Norman Douglas, Jr. (Box-folder 51:2)
  - MacLeod, Norman W. (Box-folder 51:3)
  - MacLeod, Richard (Box-folder 51:4)
  - MacLeod, Robert E. (Box-folder 51:5)
  - MacLeod, Ruth (Box-folder 51:6)
  - MacLeod, Virginia L. (Box-folder 51:7)
  - McCaskill-Bell, Olive (Box-folder 51:8)
  - McLeod, Dr. Alexander (I) (Box-folder 51:9)
  - McLeod, Dr. Alexander (II) (Box-folder 51:10)
  - McLeod, Dr. Alexander (III) (Box-folder 51:11)
  - McLeod, James (Box-folder 51:12)
  - McLeod, Purdy (I) (Box-folder 51:13)
  - McLeod, Purdy (II) (Box-folder 52:1)
  - McLeod, Purdy (III) (Box-folder 52:2)
  - McLeod, Purdy (IV) (Box-folder 52:3)
  - McLeod, Purdy (V)(undated) (Box-folder 52:4)
  - McLeod, Purdy (VI)(cards) (Box-folder 52:5)
  - Norman, Peter M. (Box-folder 52:6)
  - Pearson, Frances (Box-folder 52:7)
  - Stephens, Jack McLeod (Box-folder 52:8)
  - Zewrick, Margaret (Box-folder 52:9)
  - Miscellaneous MacLeod personal correspondence (Box-folder 52:10)
- Dunvegan Foundation 1954-2009.
  This series is divided into nineteen sub-series of administrative documents, records, and items pertaining to the charitable division of Clan MacLeod Society USA. Sub-series A: Annual Giving; Sub-series B: Board of Trustees; Sub-series C: Committees; Sub-series D: Corporate Documents; Sub-series E: Correspondence; Sub-series F: Dunvegan Castle Foundation; Sub-series G: Expenses; Sub-series H: Financial-Legal Documents: General; Sub-series I: Financial-Legal Documents: Banking; Sub-series J: Financial-Legal Documents: Budgets; Sub-series K: Financial-Legal Documents: IRS; Sub-series L: Financial-Legal Documents: Statement of Accounts; Sub-series M: Financial-Legal Documents: Tax Returns; Sub-series N: Financial-Legal Documents: Trusts; Sub-series O: Financial-Legal Documents: Grants and Scholarships; Sub-series Q: Reports; Sub-series R: Workshops; Sub-series S: Miscellaneous. This series is arranged in chronological and alphabetical order.
  - Annual Giving
    - Acknowledgments for giving (Box-folder 53:1)
    - Annual giving 1979 (Box-folder 53:2)
    - Annual giving 1980 (Box-folder 53:3)
    - Annual giving 1982 (Box-folder 53:4)
    - Annual giving 1983 (Box-folder 53:5)
    - Annual giving 1984 (Box-folder 53:6)
    - Annual giving 1985 (Box-folder 53:7)
    - Annual giving 1986 (Box-folder 53:8)
    - Annual giving 1987 (Box-folder 53:9)
    - Annual giving 1988 (Box-folder 53:10)
    - Annual giving 1989 (Box-folder 53:11)
    - Annual giving 1990 (Box-folder 53:12)
    - Annual giving 1991 (Box-folder 53:13)
    - Annual giving 1992 (Box-folder 53:14)
    - Annual giving 1993 (Box-folder 53:15)
    - Annual giving 1994 (Box-folder 53:16)
    - Annual giving 1995 (Box-folder 54:1)
    - Annual giving 1996 (Box-folder 54:2)
    - Annual giving 1997 (Box-folder 54:3)
    - Annual giving 1998 (Box-folder 54:4)
    - Deferred giving (Box-folder 54:5)
    - Donations (undated) (Box-folder 54:6)
    - Dunvegan Foundation contribution areas (Box-folder 54:7)
    - Dunvegan Foundation opportunities and recognition for giving (Box-folder 54:8)
    - Fund raising software correspondence-FM Light with demo copy of software on 5 one-fourth inch disk (rejected) (Box-folder 54:9)
    - List of contributors January 1, 1977 to September 15, 1982 (Box-folder 54:10)
    - List of contributors December 1, 1981 to May 16, 1984 (Box-folder 54:11)
    - Donors 1988 and 1989 (Box-folder 54:12)
    - Five year summary report of Dunvegan Foundation donations by region and member 1986-1991 (Box-folder 54:13)
    - Planned giving program (Box-folder 54:14)
    - Pledge cards, envelopes, brochures, acknowledgement cards (blank) (Box-folder 54:15)
    - Pledge/donation cards 1981 (Box-folder 54:16)
    - Pledge/donation cards 1982 (Box-folder 54:17)
    - Pledge/donation cards 1983 (Box-folder 54:18)
    - Pledge/donation cards 1984 (Box-folder 54:19)
    - Hold Fast Club: correspondence and information (Box-folder 54:20)
    - Prestige Club (Box-folder 54:21)
    - Questions You May Have (Box-folder 54:22)